( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
So now
والآن
you've really changed your mind about Ren,
لقد غيرت رأيك حقاً بشأن رين،
right?
يمين؟
Yes.
نعم.
I deeply regret what I've done.
أشعر بندم شديد على ما فعلت.
I feel very guilty.
أشعر بذنب شديد.
I'll find a way
سأجد طريقة
to make up for my mistakes.
لأعوض عن أخطائي.
Li Xiang's love changed you, right?
حب لي شيانغ غيّرك، أليس كذلك؟
I'll go with you to turn yourself in.
سأذهب معك لتسليم نفسك.
We'll expose
سنكشف
all the dirty business
كل الأعمال القذرة
of the Special Administration Bureau.
مكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
If you get locked up,
إذا تم حبسك،
I'll bring you good food every day.
سأحضر لك طعاماً جيداً كل يوم.
Oh right,
أوه صحيح،
Li Xiang too.
لي شيانغ أيضا.
We'll visit you together.
سنزوركم معاً.
Whoa.
يا إلهي!
You're really trying to send me to prison.
أنت تحاول حقاً إرسالي إلى السجن.
I need to record this moment.
أحتاج إلى تسجيل هذه اللحظة.
My sister tries to stab me in the back.
تحاول أختي أن تطعنني في ظهري.
Kiss stamp.
ختم القبلة.
You're the best brother.
أنت أفضل أخ.
Look at this.
انظر إلى هذا.
I deeply regret what I've done.
أشعر بندم شديد على ما فعلت.
I feel very guilty.
أشعر بذنب شديد.
I'll find a way
سأجد طريقة
to make up for my mistakes.
لأعوض عن أخطائي.
Siyuan is sorting out
سيوان يقوم بترتيب الأمور
the evidence of the bureau's crime he has.
لديه الأدلة على جريمة المكتب.
Everything's happening for us,
كل شيء يسير على ما يرام بالنسبة لنا،
right?
يمين؟
Maybe one day,
ربما في يوم من الأيام،
you'll forgive him too.
ستسامحه أنت أيضاً.
Right?
يمين؟
Give me some more time to think about it.
أعطني المزيد من الوقت لأفكر في الأمر.
Do you want the first two fragments?
هل تريد أول جزأين؟
[Recipient: Xia Shang Do you want the first two fragments?]
[المستلم: شيا شانغ، هل تريد الجزأين الأولين؟]
[Director Xia]
[المخرج شيا]
Let's meet.
لنلتقي.
These are fragments I got from my sister.
هذه بعض القطع التي حصلت عليها من أختي.
Have the tech department verify them
اطلب من قسم التقنية التحقق منها
immediately.
في الحال.
Siyuan,
سيوان،
I'm glad
أنا سعيد
you chose the greater good
لقد اخترت الصالح العام
over your family.
على عائلتك.
No.
لا.
I still chose them.
مع ذلك، اخترتهم.
I surrendered these fragments
سلمت هذه الشظايا
so you won't hurt my sister and Xie Xinxu.
حتى لا تؤذي أختي وشي شينشو.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
But we need to raise the stakes.
لكننا بحاجة إلى رفع مستوى التحدي.
Anyone who has betrayed me
كل من خانني
can't be left alive.
لا يمكن تركه على قيد الحياة.
You must disappear
يجب أن تختفي
along with these fragments.
إلى جانب هذه الشظايا.
You killed Li Xiang.
لقد قتلت لي شيانغ.
That's basically a death sentence for me.
هذا بمثابة حكم بالإعدام بالنسبة لي.
That's very different.
هذا مختلف تماماً.
What I want is
ما أريده هو
immediate.
مباشر.
But if your sister finds out
لكن إذا اكتشفت أختك ذلك
you died by my hand,
لقد متّ على يدي،
she'll come after me.
ستلاحقني.
And I can't touch her.
ولا أستطيع لمسها.
That gives me a headache though.
لكن هذا يسبب لي صداعاً.
I won't let her know.
لن أدعها تعرف.
If you don't agree,
إذا كنت لا توافق،
I can protect her another way.
أستطيع حمايتها بطريقة أخرى.
My people can hand your evidence over
بإمكان رجالي تسليم أدلتك
to higher-ups at any time.
إلى المسؤولين الأعلى رتبة في أي وقت.
I remember (Watch on www,kisskh,id or www,kisskh,la to support Admin)
أتذكر (شاهد على www.kisskh.id أو www.kisskh.la لدعم الإدارة)
there's an abandoned building
يوجد مبنى مهجور
near the bureau, right?
بالقرب من المكتب، أليس كذلك؟
How about you die there
ما رأيك أن تموت هناك؟
during a mission?
أثناء مهمة؟
Sounds good?
ًيبدو جيدا؟
You're far more terrifying than a Ren.
أنت أكثر رعباً بكثير من رين.
They were forced to become weapons.
لقد أُجبروا على أن يصبحوا أسلحة.
But you choose to be a villain
لكنك اخترت أن تكون شريراً
of your own will.
بإرادتك الخاصة.
[Emergency contact you linked]
[جهة الاتصال في حالات الطوارئ التي أرفقتها]
[is detected to be in a dangerous location]
[تم اكتشاف وجوده في موقع خطير]
Siyuan's in danger.
سيوان في خطر.
Wait.
انتظر.
It's dangerous.
إنه أمر خطير.
You stay here.
ستبقى هنا.
I'll look for him.
سأبحث عنه.
You
أنت
really surprise me.
لقد فاجأني ذلك حقاً.
If you die,
إذا مت،
Nongyu will be heartbroken.
سينكسر قلب نونغيو.
Looks like
يبدو أن
Nongyu made the right choice picking you.
لقد أحسن نونغيو الاختيار باختيارك.
You did care about her.
لقد كنت تهتم لأمرها.
As expected
كما هو متوقع
of my most beloved creation.
من أكثر إبداعاتي المحبوبة.
I didn't know
لم أكن أعرف
the bond between us
الرابطة بيننا
had grown this deep.
لقد نما إلى هذا العمق.
Now,
الآن،
I'll return the freedom
سأعيد الحرية
I owe you.
أنا مدين لك.
Let me tell you a secret.
دعني أخبرك سراً.
The day your parents died,
يوم وفاة والديك،
I sent a squad to your house.
أرسلت فرقة إلى منزلك.
Siyuan!
سيوان!
I'll probably leave you
سأتركك على الأرجح
with a huge mess to deal with.
مع وجود فوضى عارمة يجب التعامل معها.
But this is the last time.
لكن هذه هي المرة الأخيرة.
Sorry to trouble you.
أعتذر عن الإزعاج.
Take your time dealing with it.
خذ وقتك في التعامل مع الأمر.
So that's the ending.
إذن هذه هي النهاية.
Feels kind of empty.
يبدو المكان خالياً نوعاً ما.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Let's pick another show.
لنختر برنامجاً آخر.
I'll watch it all the way through with you this time.
سأشاهده معك حتى النهاية هذه المرة.
♪You had a dream inside your head♪
♪كان لديك حلم في رأسك♪
♪Wrote the story's end♪
♪كتبتُ نهاية القصة♪
♪But wrote it in the sand♪
♪لكنها كُتبت على الرمال♪
♪The face in your fairy tale looked like me♪
♪الوجه في حكايتك الخيالية يشبهني♪
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
No!
لا!
Siyuan!
سيوان!
Why didn't you grab him just now?
لماذا لم تمسك به الآن؟
I...
أنا...
I froze.
تجمدت في مكاني.
Don't risk your life.
لا تخاطر بحياتك.
Let go of me.
اتركني وشأني.
Let go!
اتركه!
You didn't even want to save him, did you?
لم تكن تريد حتى إنقاذه، أليس كذلك؟
No.
لا.
Because he just told me
لأنه أخبرني للتو
that he was involved in my parents' deaths.
أنه كان متورطاً في وفاة والديّ.
It's already too late to save him now.
لقد فات الأوان لإنقاذه الآن.
Your brother did so many terrible things.
لقد فعل أخوك أشياءً فظيعة كثيرة.
Didn't he deserve to die?
ألم يكن يستحق الموت؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
let's just pretend
لنتظاهر فقط
he never existed.
لم يكن موجوداً أبداً.
We'll only have each other, okay?
لن يكون لدينا سوى بعضنا البعض، حسناً؟
You're a cold monster.
أنت وحش بارد.
What makes you think I'd choose you over my brother?
ما الذي يجعلك تعتقد أنني سأختارك على أخي؟
Since I'm not your first choice,
بما أنني لست خيارك الأول،
there's no reason for me to put you at the center of my world.
ليس هناك أي سبب يدفعني لوضعك في مركز عالمي.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
I will do things my way.
سأفعل الأمور على طريقتي.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪